This happened absolutely powder senior position within
me hello chal laga position ok so I will
talk about this insurance thing if you
heard the whole story Anurag I
want to take your opinion on that this
third party free in chosen insurance is
not increasing for motor insurance people
this should be considered positive
for the insurance company you have also made a romantic comment from ICU just now these are the
news so that
possible different also taken from the insurance company
and ICICI Lombard is a very big and active company in the development of the nation
this is a very big
and active company in motor insurance but the stock is very
good anyway Virat so I had a long term
view on this a proposal of 1650 comes to him
evening corrupt and on such news
it seems that only from here in very
small also from here this
current news of youth from the left side should be absolutely cool
that you should go for buying and now let us